franklincovey.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy | FRANKLINCOVEY

Franklin Covey is committed to protecting your personal information and strives to take appropriate measures to protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains what information Franklin Covey Co. ("Franklin Covey") collects from users of its services and the franklincovey.com website (the "Site") and how we use this information.

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES FRANKLIN COVEY COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED?

Franklin Covey collects personal information through its Site in connection with user registration and purchase of goods/services offered on the Site, including contact information (i.e., name, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and billing information) and demographic information (i.e., ZIP code, gender or age). We use this information to send our users information about our Site and to contact the user when necessary.

When providing personal information about anyone other than himself or herself, the user will obtain the other person’s consent and provide that person access to this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, Franklin Covey or its business affiliates may also use your registration information to send you offers and promotions that may be of interest to you. By providing your contact information, you give us permission to send you such materials. Users may opt-out of receiving certain future mailings. See the choice/opt-out section below. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected during registration. We use this data to tailor the user's experience at Franklin Covey to show users interesting content and to display content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

## DOES FRANKLIN COVEY SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Franklin Covey may release personal information when we: (1) respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, and to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Use or as otherwise required by law; or (3) transfer information about you if Franklin Covey is acquired by or merged with another entity.

We may provide personal information to third parties for their use in performing internal functions on our behalf (for example, payment processing, maintenance, security, data analysis, hosting, and so forth). In such instances, the providers will be contractually required to protect personal information from additional use (including for marketing purposes) or transfer in accordance with this Privacy Policy and industry standards.

Occasionally, we make our customer list available to a few carefully screened firms offering products that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive such mailings or not to have your information shared in this manner, you may opt-out at any time. See the choice/opt-out section below.

## CHOICE/OPT-OUT

Our Site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Franklin Covey through our Unsubscribe page. Please allow 45 days for your opt-out request to take effect. Note that regardless of your opt-out selections, Franklin Covey may continue to correspond with you, via e-mail and other means of communications, in connection with your customer relationship with Franklin Covey.

## CORRECT/UPDATE ADDRESS

If you would like to change or update your personal information please visit the Change of Address page.

## TRANSFERS OF PERSONAL DATA

FranklinCovey transfers information outside of the country of origin in the delivery of its services, including to the United States of America. By accepting these terms and conditions, you expressly consent to allow Franklin Covey to transfer personal data (including, but not limited to, name, title and e-mail address) utilizing the services to other countries, including the United States of America, that may have less stringent laws regarding data protection than the laws in the in your jurisdiction

## PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Franklin Covey uses technical and organizational measures to protect the personal information we receive against loss, misuse, and unauthorized alteration and to protect its confidentiality. We regularly review our security procedures and consider appropriate new security technology and methods. We also use current encryption technology to encrypt the transmission of data on our log-in pages.

## HOW DOES FRANKLIN COVEY USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you access the Site. We may set and access cookies on your computer and use web beacons, clear GIFs or similar technologies to provide us with information about your browsing experience. We may also allow other companies that show advertisements on our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies.

We use this information collected to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site, as well as to deliver content tailored to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to reenter it each time you visit our Site.

If you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed on your computer. Note that some features of our Site may not be available if you do not accept cookies.

## HOW DOES FRANKLIN COVEY WORK WITH OTHER COMPANIES AND HOW DO THESE RELATIONSHIPS AFFECT USER PRIVACY?

The Site contains links to other websites. Franklin Covey does not control the privacy policies of business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other websites to which Franklin Covey provides hyperlinks.

Occasionally we share user’s personal information collected on our Site with our sponsors and partners. In this regard, we share such information on an aggregate basis and do not reveal information about individual users of the Site without consent.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Site, the ad company collects cookies received with banner ads. We do not have access to this information, nor control the use of their cookies or the use of information collected by such company.

## WHAT IS FRANKLIN COVEY'S POLICY REGARDING POSTS ON MESSAGE BOARDS?

Franklin Covey message boards are available to all Site users. Please remember any information disclosed in public message boards becomes public information; therefore, you should exercise caution when disclosing personal information.

## USE OF SITE BY MINORS

The Site is intended for adult use only. In connection with the Site, Franklin Covey does not promote online to children and does not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Franklin Covey strives to comply with and adhere to the FTC’s Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.

## RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA

We retain collected personal information and usage data for a reasonable period to fulfill the collection purposes and provide the requested services, with the exception of limited profile information which is retained as part of a permanent user profile.

## HOW TO CONTACT US

Franklin Covey has a data privacy officer who helps ensure compliance with this Privacy Policy, educates us on privacy matters and answers data privacy questions. Inquiries about this Privacy Policy or the use of your personal information by Franklin Covey may be sent by [list methods] to the following:

  * E-mail:
  * Phone:
  * Address:

## CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

We regularly review the Privacy Policy and may change it as needed. When we modify the Policy, we will update the effective date below. If there are material changes to the way Franklin Covey uses your personal information, we will notify you here on this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to learn how Franklin Covey is protecting your information.

## EFFECTIVE DATE

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 01/28/2016.
